Edited at https://subtitletools.com
doramon, part1
it's such a wonderful thing
I wish it might come true
this kind of dream, that kind of dream
many kinds of dreams
all of them can come true
incredible pocket makes
your dreams come true
I wanna fly in the sky
no problem
bamboo drangonfly
on, on, on , my favorite
doramon
dream city,nobita'+C77s fantacy land
watch this
I am good
you are great
get out of my way
go away
doramon, hang on
nobody skates at home
but it's dangerous to skate outside
it is, and there is no skating place to go
gee
kid, you wanna die
can't do
eh, what's wrong? Sitsika
I wanted to play at home
but my mom said there was a tea gathering
at home and wanted me to come out
if you have nothing to do
let's play dodge ball
ok
great, let’s play
enter prohibited
xx construction company
why is that
can't get in, why not
you can tell that
they are building lots of buildings
this place became a material place, moron
we came all the way
I am so disappointed
so where can we paly
ouch, it hurts
why do you do this to me
I want it so badly
want what
my own house
no, my own city
no matter when or where
I can do whatever I want to do
I wish there was a city like this
freedom city
ok,let's build one
build one? A city
now let's build up our own house
mini polaroid camera
take pictures first
and wait for them to be developed
pour some hot water and wait for 3 seconds
done
it's a model house
even the furnitures are the same
what can you do to this kind of toy house
no problem
just make it bigger
what, I see
can we really do that
just get into this mini tunnel
see, that's how it works, we made it
this is fun
just get into the tunnel
you can live in that house then
I want to take pictures for all the houses
doramon
it's getting like a city
yes, now just arrange them the way you like
what's this
such a tiny book
the words in it are so tiny like ants
but where are the people living inside
people can't be taken in
the picture, so don‘t worry
let's have streets here
but no traffice lights and zebra crossings
also, bowling place and baseball field
let's make video game shops too
doramon, go take some more pictures
I will get everybody here
see you in a bit
nobita,C136 we are so bored
what's wrong with you
the way you laugh is so weird
everybody, let me
make your dream come true, follow me
is there really a place like that? No way
I won't forgive you if you lie
here is the entry
you want us to get into
this place, don’t fool us
shut up
please get in
ok
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
my god
it's awesome
this is our city
ouch, it hurts
let us join
you eat too much dumplings
you will have a stomachache
give me the toy model
get whatever you want, suit yourself
l have been dreaming laying down
on the street and sleep like this
I am tired of palying around
read some comics
everyone is having fun at playing
this place is called
nobita's dream land+C11O
my god
it's mom
help
there is so much garbage here, how clumsy
let's have a small warehouse here
ok
nobita's dream land is gone
doramon, get something
that you can make a free land
please
if you don't behave well
you will cause lots of trouble
it's impossible to make up some land
nobita
go clean up the trash can
it's not my business
doramon should do that
what is that
no way
transform cookie
nobita
go buy some deserts to treat our guests
what a trouble
by the way
doramon, gotta go shopping
doramon
what's wrong, is he out
what's this
animal cookies
I'll take this
ok
sorry
sorry for waiting
what
why cookies
it's ok, I love cookies
nobita
go buy some nice stuff
yes
this and this, and this as well
here is the change
ok
it‘s correct
what do you want keeping staring at my face
kitty
is this my face
doramon, help
doramon
what, she ate that cookie
that's animal transform cookie
you can eat it like that
what am I going to be
what's now, meow
it takes sometime
to transform after you eat it
but you will transform back in 5 minutes
really
see
you are right
you gave them to the guest
that's not a good thing
I don't know if she had it or not
did you eat this?
|
do you feel any difference
are you ok
you had 4, what are you talking about
you are rude
what do we do now
doramon is there anything
that we can stop transforming
no
my god
this
he must have eaten the horse shape cookie
ok
sir, please come over here
there is a very important thing
it's the dressing room
thanks
nobita
where are the cookies you bought
I left them at the lobby
great
don't know if you like it or not
how delicate the desert is
this time it's chicken
sir, go to the dressing room again
have you done yet
gotta do something
sir, your phone
this phone
it's on the way
who is this
I am just a nobody
what are you talking about
let‘s chat, just for 1 hour
what, I don't know
what you are talking about
don't know
who played this joke on me, I am puzzled
wait, it's not changing back yet
| see
no, don't look, mom, don‘t
don't
nobita
what are you doing in front of the guest
I won't let you go
damn, where are you
it's about time for me to leave
sorry, nothing really fancy to treat you
sir
sir, stay for a while
one more
no, I am leaving
it appeared
now mom is angry
yes
I am shivering, I can't move
it's dad
I am home
what did you do again
| see
I will apologize to your mom for you
I am home
mom ate some tOO
shit, what should I do now
lam in trouble now
shit, fuck, what
you doramon, I hate you
lam in a hurry and you don’t care at all
why are you in a hurry
good question
there are japanese test
and math test tomorrow
so that’s why you are carrying
your pillow and water bottle
shit
it has nothing to do with the tests
but after all lam
like this is because I feel shitty
super shitty,
what
help me out
you are not going to just sit ther
and do nothing, right, doramon
please help me
I will get 0 on my score like this
please
just use this fan, you wanna help me
doramon is the best
tell me about it
use that to blow off the school
I am appreciated
blow off the school
what kind ofjoke is that
can't do
do something else
use like animal light to turn
the teacher into a gorilla
thanks
would you be serious
what
you are the one who don't work hard
it's your own fault
I will study hard, this time
please rescue me
please do something
if I get 0 on my score
I will run away from house
all right, all right
let me use the printing bread
printing bread
press the bread on the book and the content
on the book will be print onto the bread
and eat it up
then you will remember
all the things on this page
do you wanna try
what is multipled by 2 and equals 6
bingo
what is multipled by 5 and equals 10
correct
just memorize all the exercises
from notebook and textbook
I should be ok
keep eating
I can get 100 on my score now
eh, I missed one very important page
damn, I used it to sneeze my nose last time
what are you doing
what's that
l have to print my friend's notebook
sorry, please get me more printing bread
I go to my classmate's
| see
no problem
it's no big deal to lend you
my notebook as long as I can be helpful
really, thanks
please take a look
how dirty
| work hard
you don‘t want my notebook
it's really hard to
eat this kind of printing bread
shitzika's notebook is always
this clean, lam going to take it
it won't be that hard
if everything is this easy
I am quite good at memorizing things
you are the most forgetful person in class
ok, let me show you
for example, this telephone book
I can memorize all on the first page
test me
please start
name it
what's the telephone number of mr. Abc
1234567
you are right
what about mr. Def
9999876
you are right, awesome
no big deal
it's hard not to get 100
how nice
yes, as long as l have this bread
nobita, have some desert
I brought lots of mochi
nice yum mochi
I can eat a lot
you just eat and red comics
don't you study
what's wrong
l have to let the food
in my stomach digested
you have eaten too much
sorry, can I borrow your notebook
I am home
welcome home
time for dinner, come on over
I don't want to eat
how can you do that? Nobita
you are the one who
said that you wanted cheeseburger
but
you have to eat
I made a special big one for you, come eat
special big one
no, I can't eat anymore, I can't
nobita, have you memorized all
not at all
I gave you tons of printing bread
you forced me to do things I don't wanna do
I know, don't be angry
l have borrowed
the notebook back, I will eat
90909090
I really can't take it anymore
have some water and swallow it
I can't
I really can't do this anymore
is it ok to have 0 on your test
no way
I know
I will let you eat all of them by no means
are you done yet
not yet
what's wrong, come outside
nobita has been there for 1 hour
he ate too much and
is having a stomachache now
that's no good
did you get rid of all the stuff you ate
so you have to eat from page 1 now
ns clilp
come on over
come check this out, it's fun
look, I found something interesteing
and this can make me win the nobel award
once the n ends of the maganent
approach closer they just bounce away
so do s ends
if s end and n end get closer
see, they stick together
it's fun, I found it
who doesn’t know that
I knew it when I was at the kindergarten
you are retarded
asshole
help
stop
asshole
you embarrassed me in front of everyone
stop , nobita, stop
it's ok, I won't forget
if you show up in front of me
, I will beat you hard
you keep it in mind
nobita,you keep it in mind
who told you to be so talktive
doramon, do something, help me, please
what can I do
you live in the same neighborhood
and go to same school
no matter how, you will meet
yes, there is a way that you dont
have to see each other
are you going to show me something
it's NS clip
what are those for
if you put this on
you will be like a maganet
s ends go together
vise verse
let’s try
first, you have to put it on
then
here let‘s have one too
dad asked you to see him
really
what’s up , dad
you
see, same ends don't
what are you doing
I don't care
why are you mad
ouch
come, grab my hand
no
mom
mom, what are you doing
I am not happy about it
your body just bounced away
how ridiculous, you don't like me anymore
mom, don‘t run
why are you two fighting
what should we do
now the only way is to
change one of the clips
it's weird, there is no way to approach it
mom
done, it's great
now you understand
you stick s on you
and giant too with s
now let me go stick this on him
lse
so giant can't get close to me
are you sick, hang around on the streets
I am not afriad
giant said he is going to tear you up
just show me
now something is going to be happening
just let giant to find him, show time
what
nobita thatjerk, I am going to tear him up
giant, nobita is walking
toward that direction
ok
show time
stop right there, nobita
asshole, nobita, don't run
come on over
nobita
it's so close
where is the clip
it's not on him yet
not yet, you kid
I got you
asshole
nobita became very quick
this is convenient
it fits lots of places
by the way, give me more clips
why do you need them
here you are
lam going to do some great things
where is shitzika
shitzika
stop it
let him go
so it's wont be bounced away
show you this
ns clip is powerful
shitzika
shit, I am wrong, I should stick this
sorry, shitzika
why is that,don’t come over
just switch mine
I can't take it off
take off your clothes
eh, where is sitzika
sitzika
don't worry, come out now
where are you
sitzika
it's giant
help
doramon, help me out, do something
move giant away
if you can't, just switch giant and sitzika
hurry up, doramon
sitzika
say something
I told you not to use it to joke around
I don't won't to care about you anymore
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
wrestling killer
I am leaving
I am late
watch out, bummer
open your eyes walking
what, you bumped into me
I have no time for this
I am so late
you were late huh
it's all your fault
I wish I could get up earlier
then it wouldn't happen to me
and I wouldn't be late
if so, if I wan't being pushed down by giant
I would be able to make it
I hate this
you are such a baby,
let's try this wrestling killer
professional killer
no, not professional killer
not professional killer
it's wrestling killer
| see, you scared me
but what 's a wrestling killer
like it's name, he wrestles people
just put 10 yen into it
and call a name who you hate,
it sounds boring
but it's a great tool to revenge giant
true, let me hire wrestling killer
with 10 yen
let's give giant a hard time
that's right, exactly
he is an expert
he will make giant trippen 3 times
let's see
he walks like an expert
does he know where giant is
what the hell are you
asshole, you little kid
trying to give me a hard time
you don't know
where you position is, watch me
ouch
go away
stay away from me
great
help
no
leave me alone
please
he is quite an expert
he is really mean trying on wrestling
good, from now on, I am going to use this
to give those people
who are trying to give me a hard time
I got you
ouch
you did this to me, just watch
let me show you my wrestling killer
nobita
what are you doing
don't call my name now
no, it's not me, no
uncle cop
help me out
doramon
god, finally, I get rid of him
what happened, why are you like this
it's so scary, here is the story
no, can't do
once the wrestling killer gets the order
it will fullfill it now matter how
what, what should I do now
put 100 yen in and he will stop
what, I have spent 20 yens already
so you just wait to be trippen
here I come
who is this
I do it , I have 100 yen
go cancel it, count on e
here I come,
please don't tear my house down
I go get it
cancel
100 yen
ok now
l have canceled
I spent 120 yen, what a deal
it wasn't easy to cancel it
why did you fall off
nobita's bride
this baby
is this big alreay
time flies
now he is a student
happy birthday
thanks
soon he will be junior high student
then, senior high, college
if he can make it
shut up
after college, he will be an adult
then he will get married
bride
if someone wants to marry you
are you done or not
I am telling the truth, doramon, stop it
stop it
no one is going to marry you
no way, stop it
stop it
but
I am kind of worried
about what
what if I can't marry someone
what should I do
you are really worried about it huh
if you are really that worried
why don't you check it out yourself
check out what
use time machine to go the future
to see my bride
yes, my bride
no good, I will be shy
forget it then
I wanna see
do you wanna see it or not
here we are
in the bathroom
bathroom everywhere
my house became a bathroom
the streets are different
it was nobita's house
they have moved here for 10 years
it's a park now
that's the building
no. 68, the 12th floor, I am so excited
lam nervous, who is my bride
lam knocking on the door
wait, doramon, hang on
it's not a good idea to meet like this
TRUE
I just have a peek on it
use this mirror
you can see through by this
I saw it, but only the back
my god
I don't want to be like that, do something
there is nothing I can do
why is it so slow
where is ms. Nobita
it's awful, how can it be like this
my future is so sad
I got you , you are really naughty
unless you are
shitzuka 25 years ago
why did you say this to your mom
come in with me
this is
here comes the future mom
say sorry to him
sung always like to give our
taron a hard time
my kid is too naughty
please educate your kid, ms. Nobita
next time I won't be this nice
I am truly sorry
the sung guy is exactly like me
he is my son
then his mom is sitzuka, meaning
meaning
yeah
great, so it's you
how can you act like this to your mom, wait
your dad is so quiet and a honest person
and why are you so different
damn, ouch, it hurts
ouch
I am home
I got it, so he is sung
who are you , why are you at my house
sung, don't be naughty
did you work hard at school
stop it, sung
you ca'nt do this to your dad, what dad
you must be an alien
coming here to occupy my house
help
stop it, alien
stop it
go back to the time machine
someone is there
open up the door, open up
no
hw mean
he is too energetic
my god
where have you been
sitzuka is here for you
happy birthday, nobita
thanks
why are you shy all of a sudden
weird kid
doramon's prediction
I am home
I am out
it's the magic hand of 22 century
doramon, don't fool around
I gotta stop you no matter how
you are going to see sitzuka now, right
yes
she is bored at home alone so she wants
you to go to her house to play with her
you know it well huh
you can't go
don't do that, leave me alone
ok, I will let you go and you will see
see, your future photo album
you got hit on your way to her house
it takes you 1 month to recover
you are not so smart at the first place
and it's getting worse
really
so you'd better stay home all day today
sitzuka will be angry
nobita, it's sitzuka
damn, it's her
let me reject her for you
ok
hey
I am truly sorry
hey, let me say something
what, funny comics and special made cake
did you reject her for me
tell you the truth, I told her you are
on your way to her house
bummer
is it ok if I get hit
it's ok since I will go with you, let's go
there are cake and comics there
what
nothing, lets go
wait, be careful
time tv
where will we be in 10 seconds
run, that's the place
it's dangerous if we go that way
it's ok since we know it
you stepped on our toy
it's kind of accident too
the danger is still there
look ahead when you walk
it might be from behind, watch out
I told you to watch ahead
behind, ahead
next, ahead, behind, next
you can't watch out all of them
at the same time
SO many cars
there is no way to go
what should I do, damn
yes, just go
go from those places without streets
sorry to come to bother you
it's a street over there
it's tough
help
here is the car
it's in the yard
you came to my private yard, are you thieves
no, there is a reason
what, just for avoiding the car
you came to the wrong place
this house is just right on the corner
so trucks crash in all the time
see
I got it, there is a street that
is definitely safe
doramon is retarded
why did you think of it earlier
you too
I can't put up with this, I wanna go home
too late, it will happen on our way home
it's destiney
this is it
why didn't I think of it
nobita, it's ok
bamboo dragonfly
put this on your head
why didn't you take out this
very convenient thing ealier
sorry
I saw sitzuka's house
sitzuka, good afternoon
stop it
sorry, I am so bored
| asked my neighbor to come over to my house
great, nobita
it's not good at all
but compare to this
it's nothing really serious
it's great
what
you are right
dinosaur hunting
I am home
what's this
lower your voice
it was not a dream
I did see it
how weird
where did it go
how funny
doramon, there was a dinosaur here just now
did you see it
you saw it
lam going to do dinosaur hunting with chun
dinosaur hunting
it's in in the future world
super funny sports
it was
to take it back to 10 billion years ago
by time machine
keep it here
so we can have dinosaur pet
sounds interesting
ok, I am in too
wait, nobita
what, it's lousy, doramon
it's a dangerous sport
you have to have strong body
and consitance quality
also guts
for me, it's not a problem
but nobita
do you have those qualities, so what
this
a mouse
gee, the mouse is awful
I am so scared
no, not the mosue
I lied
you are brave huh
strong body huh,
ok, ok, I will show you
I will be ok when you are around
you have to do something first
before you hunt dinosaurs
go get butter and jelly
yes
that's too much, only butter and jelly
why not, those are for our lunch
good, it's ok
let's set off
ouch
1O billions years ago, it's cool
but how are you going to hunt dinosaurs
doramon, tell me
count on me, I have my secret weapon
pole minimized machine
no matter what
it will become small in a second
eh, I got the wrong one
it's this
no
this
it's you bringing a lot, I got it
let me show you how powerful this machine is
cook ,it became so small
let me try
nobita, it's hard to control
it's not working
if you don't approach the dinosaur
no problem
ok, let me go get them
I feel insecure, I think we'd better go home
nobita, here comes the big one
nobita, shoot him, hurry
don’t run, nobita, shoot, hurry
nobita, no, it's enough
see, it's like an ant now
you cant make it back now
sorry
I will do it, ok
now butter and jelly
are we starting to eat
no, this
you have gone too far
you use me as a bait to put on butter
and jelly on my face and head
doramon, it showed up
see, doramon
I am experienced, I am not nervouse at all
see how calm I am
what are you doing, doramon, hurry
that's why I am different from you
I know, hurry
take it out
what now, I got the wrong one
hurry
not, not this,
I got it
help
hep
my god
it’s terrible, ia m so scared
help
run now
my glassess, no time for that
we found a dinosaur
from 10 billions years ago
you are wearing glasses the parliament
is talking about this right now
big news
there is a person with round face
there is a person with long face
there is a person with square face
there is a person with triangel face
cry, shout, be moody
you will turn into a devil
but, smile and cheer up
everybody is round faced